<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>APXTConga4__Conga_Email_Letterhead</letterhead>
    <name>Anderson Advisors -- Follow Up on Your Living Trust</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Anderson Advisors -- Follow Up on Your Living Trust</subject>
    <textOnly>Hello {!firstname},
 
We hope you are doing well! We are reaching out to you regarding the Living Trust you recently purchased from us. 
Developing an Estate Plan is one of the most important things you can do during your life. We understand that it requires a lot of decision-making and sometimes even hard choices, so, please take all the time you need to complete the Questionnaire. 
Here is the Questionnaire that we will need for you to complete in order to move forward with your Living Trust&apos;s formation. We&apos;ve also created a helpful video, which provides a brief explanation of the Questionnaire and overviews of each section. We recommend viewing this before starting the Questionnaire.
Once you have completed the Questionnaire, please submit it using one of the following methods (as the Questionnaire contains sensitive information we do not recommend returning it via email):
- Uploading directly to your Viewable Client Docs folder within Box;
- Using a direct upload service at the following link: https://andersonadvisors.com/upload-documents;
- Faxing it to us at 702.664.0545;
- Or mailing directly to us at: 3225 McLeod Drive Las Vegas, NV 89121
Once we receive your completed Questionnaire, a team member will contact you to schedule a consultation with an Estate Planning attorney. During the consultation, you will have the opportunity to ask the attorney any questions that you may have about this Questionnaire or about your Estate Planning documents.
Please be assured that your Trust will not be created until you have had the opportunity to review your Questionnaire in detail with the attorney.  We ask that you fill out the attached Questionnaire fully to give the attorney the framework for your consultation; any necessary details will be added as the attorney works with you.
Please let us know if we can be of additional assistance!


Kind Regards,</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
